(Sheldon:)They were having fun wrong.
(Priya:)Come here, Sheldon.
Sit here with me.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Priya:)Would you like some
homemade chili?
(Sheldon:)Are there beans in it?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)Then it's not chili.
(Sheldon:)Real chili has no beans in it,
(Sheldon:)but you're
from a foreign land,
(Sheldon:)so your ignorance
is forgiven.
(Priya:)Sheldon, do you want some
or not?
(Sheldon:)Yes, please.
(Sheldon:)Your girlfriend's a
little short-tempered.
(Stuart:)I'd like
to propose a toast
(Raj:)to friends,
no matter how quirky.
ALL:
Cheers.
(Sheldon:)Priya, do you know
why this is called a toast?
(Priya:)Actually, I do.
(Priya:)I believe the Romans
used to put spiced toast
(Leonard:)in their punch bowls.
(Sheldon:)She's also a bit
of a know-it-all.
(Sheldon:)Mmm. This is good.
(Sheldon:)Whatever it is.
♪ I'm walking on sunshine ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
(LeVar Burton:)Hello? I...
♪ I'm walking on sunshine ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
(LeVar Burton:)Oh, I don't think so.
(LeVar Burton:)I am so done with Twitter.